RJP respects the rape victim.  Here the lead
increased by 3000 votes over Panihati seat.   The
battle for power in West Bengal is going to be decided
today.  Counting of votes has started here.   There is churning
in Delhi and commotion in Lucknow.
New faces are going to join the Yogi cabinet.
Yes friends,
BJP can make a big claim on Brahmin and Dalit equations.
Counting continues in five states.  These votes are
not being counted.  Every
vote is important in an election, but some votes may
not be counted.  Like here,
storm alert has been issued in 38 districts of Tadi Bihar.  Yes
friends, 60 km.
Winds will blow at a speed of.  Who knows when the
scorching heat will return.   The
department is with BJP, that is why the
bridges are falling.  Yes friends, the
attack by Pappu Yadav and RJD has started due to the collapse of Vikramshila Setu.   The
third meeting of the Emperor Cabinet will be held on May 6
and will focus on major decisions and new policies.  The
Chief Minister will be on a visit to Delhi.
Tourism has changed the BPSC exam.  Now the
exam will be conducted in two phases.  Know
what is the new plan of the Commission.
Scam in Chief Minister Jan Awas Yojana and allotment lottery of 3081 plots here.   There was an uproar
after the UIT Secretary was punished.
Big changes in the country from May.  Can be withdrawn through UPI.
Here the limit of PF money will be this much.
IMD warns that the scorching heat will now torment the nation
and heatwave alert has been issued in seven states, including Delhi and UP.
Nights will also be
extremely hot.
India has to pay double the price for urea here.  The
government had ordered a record
import of 25 tonnes of lac here.
Online crimes against women are increasing
daily, 370 cases are on top, fake profiles,
obscene messages are also increasing the problem,
online map on Delhi Dehradun Express
can deceive you, be careful here,
land owners in Darbhanga are shocked by the government's decision, will
not be able to sell their plots till 2027,
US Navy
Secretary John Fallon suddenly left his post amid tension with Iran,
doors of Badrinath temple opened.  CM Dhami performed the
puja and thousands of Sardars
became witnesses in the holy person here.
45 names deleted from voter list in Nadi village, West Bengal.  Yes friends, let me
tell you here that 90% are Muslims.
Know the complete reason behind this with us.
Asha Bhosle cannot be divided into India and Pakistan,
Hanif's blog.   The
heat wave in Delhi crossed 53 degrees.  The
air quality deteriorated and the weather department
issued this major warning.
Malika Arjun Khadege scored an
electoral self-goal by calling PM Modi a terrorist.
Three are conspiring.
24 Chinese aircraft and eight ships were seen here in Taiwan.
Congress hits back at BJP on women reservation.
This command was handed over to women leaders across the country.
Tax on entry of commercial vehicles increased in Delhi.  New rates will be applicable from today.
Know complete information in this video.
Cyber ​​fraud of Rs 2500 crore,
20 arrested including three bank officials.  85 fake
accounts exposed.
Why are Congress and experts here accusing PM Modi's address to the nation of being
used for political purposes?   An
attempt will be made to resolve it or a bill will be introduced.
What is the government's next plan after the Women's Reservation Bill was defeated in the Lok Sabha?
Schools in Maharashtra that do not teach Marathi language will be derecognized.  Yes
friends, strict action will be taken for violating the rules.
Instructions to impose fines on illegal parking and encroachment on National Highway.  road
safety.  Here, AC took a big stance.   A
15-year-old girl filed a complaint in the Amravati sexual abuse case.  More
matters will come to light.
Congress is anti-women;
after the fall of the reservation bill, the central government made a
big attack on the opposition;
what is known so far about the firing on ships flying the Indian flag; Trump
asked the question,
we want a house in exchange for a house;
why did the villagers
oppose the Betwa project; know the complete details in this video;
ED took action before the Bengal elections;
raid started at Sinha's house, close to Mamata Banerjee;
Iran refused to hold direct talks in America.
You will be surprised to know this big reason.
I challenge Prime Minister Modi that what is
Ashok Gehlot saying on PM Modi's apology.
Palgram police is giving QR code.   The
entire horoscope will appear before the tourist as soon as it is scanned.   There may be a
big shock for those travelling to Delhi
as the government is planning to increase the entry charges.
Now
IndiGo has issued an advisory for passengers
and here is the information about the flight operations affected due to bad weather in Delhi.   A
woman from Bengal has escaped from police custody in Mumbai.  She ran away with her
husband on the pretext of going to the washroom.
Shocking figures have emerged in the merit list of police constable recruitment in Haryana.  Let us
tell you that the
cut off for general category was 52 and for EWS category it was 71.
Relief from rain in UP and Delhi.
Heatwave alert in Madhya Pradesh, IMD
told when the heat will return.
Navneet Rana cried over the non-passage of the Women's Reservation Bill and said that the opposition has
snatched the rights of women.
Priyanka Gandhi mentioned Chanakya.
PM Modi said that there will be no injustice.   A
heated debate broke out among the Parliament over the delimitation bill.
Praising Pakistan, Donald Trump has
said that I am also going to
Islamabad.
Noida administration accepted the main demands,
why is there still fear among the workers and
disappointment is also visible here.  Know the
complete information.   Is
Nitish Kumar's decision to go to Rajya Sabha
for Janata Dal United or is there
some other issue?   Will
not extend the discount on buying oil from Russia.
What will be the impact of America on India?
Know the complete information.
Women's Reservation Bill: PM Modi said that
those opposing it today will have to
pay the price for it for a long time.
Nitish Kumar's resignation from the post of CM,
how much has Bihar changed in 21 years of rule, know the
complete details further in this video,
Pakistan's decision to return billions of rupees loan to UAE,
what is its connection with Saudi Arabia,
cabinet meeting of Hemant government's Lambi government is
going on, equation will be implemented here with the politics of pain and medicine,
discussion on constitutional amendment will continue today,
opposition leader Rahul Gandhi will put forth his views in the Lok Sabha,
Delimitation Bill will be passed in the Parliament today.  Yes
friends, Congress is saying that there is share
theft, so here Starlin talked about showing black flags.
BJP finally got the fruits of its patience in Bihar.
Will running the alliance be a challenge?   The
timing of the billion-dollar loan Pakistan received from Saudi Arabia.  Why is it so important?
Know the complete information.
Why are questions being raised about the proposal to increase the number of Lok Sabha seats to 850 for 33% women reservation?
Two of the three meaningful drop bills that the central government sent to MPs on Tuesday are starting to make
major historical changes.
Reports of death or disappearance of 10 scientists have come to light in America.  Yes
friends, let me tell you that after the report, during the
discussion on the matter, a journalist
asked here in the Tweet House that why these cases are
not being thoroughly investigated?   The
High Court deadline has been completed today.  If the
elections are postponed till next year, the Commission
's problems will increase.
Friends, let us tell you that the deadline given by the High Court for the Panchayat elections in Rajasthan will
expire on Wednesday and this year, that is, the
elections were to be held but did not take place, the preparations of the
State Election Commission for the voting lists will remain in limbo.   It
is difficult to extend the booking rule within 25 days.  The cylinder is getting finished in 15 to 20 days.  Yes
friends, let me tell you that the
people here have found a new way. The
LPG crisis is
taking a serious form in the capital Jaipur and to streamline the gas supply here, the
rule of booking one gas cylinder for 25 days has been implemented.
Fast attack will be implemented on Delhi Dehradun Express.
Yes friends, how much will
your toll be on annual pass. Let me tell you that Dehradun
Express is 213 km long and there are
six lines here as well and the
new Chaudhary of Bihar will be Samrat. Yes
friends, just before Nitish's resignation,
some stir is happening in Bihar.  BJP is going to
make its own CM here in Bihar for the first time.
Severe heat wave continues in Rajasthan.   The
temperature in Barmer and Jaisalmer has crossed 41 degrees.  There will
be heatwave alert in these districts.
Narendra Modi will reach the public meeting venue in some time.  Slogans of Narendra Modi will be raised.  Let us
tell you that Modi will inaugurate Delhi Express
and Dehradun Express from here.
After this,
Prime Minister Narendra Modi will address the public meeting.
Why is Mamata Banerjee telling TMC workers
that they will be arrested?  Let us tell you
friends that
before the assembly elections in West Bengal, Chief Minister Mamata
Banerjee has asked the Trinamool Congress workers
and her supporters to keep the common people alert.
Maulana Khalid Rashid's
special appeal to Muslims before Census 2027.  Let me tell you that my
religion is Islam and my mother tongue is
Urdu.  Yes friends,
regarding the upcoming digital census in the country, the
Uttar Pradesh Secondary Education Board in the city of Lucknow
can soon announce the date of High School and Internet examination i.e. result 2026.  Yes friends, let us tell you
that the evaluation of copies is
in the final stage.
What negative is BJP doing here during Amit Shah's 15-day visit to Bengal?
Yes friends, let us tell you that Trinamool
Congress has jokingly said that
Amit Shah can try staying here for 365 days.
But here there is not going to be
any significant improvement in the position of BJP in Bengal.
Metro in Jaipur will run
41 km without driver by 2031.  The corridor will be ready and
36 stations will be ready here.